<blog>
	<post>
		<date>APril 22, 2022</date>
		<author>Jordan Raanan</author>
		<title id = 1 >Giant's Toney Missing from Practice</title>
		<summary>New York Giants WR Kadarius Toney could be available in a trade, source says</summary>
		<body>New York Giants first-round pick Kadarius Toney could be available in a trade, a source confirmed to ESPN.

The New York Daily News first reported Toney might be being shopped by new GM Joe Schoen.

Toney was the 20th overall pick last year out of Florida. He had a rocky rookie season that included multiple injuries and situations, from wearing the wrong-sized cleats to skipping the voluntary offseason program to multiple positive COVID-19 tests, that keep him off the field.

In 2021, Toney played in 10 games, catching 39 passes for 420 yards and no touchdowns.

Schoen has been adamant since being hired about exploring all options. He mentioned being willing to listen to offers for just about everyone, including running back Saquon Barkley, at the NFL scouting combine.

The first-year general manager has since said that was blown out of proportion. Schoen spoke to Barkley immediately afterwards and has since said he did not make any calls about trading the star running back, even if he did receive some.

But Schoen did say at the combine he didn't view Toney as a tradable piece and expected him to be on the team this season.

Toney hasn't been at voluntary offseason workouts or this past week's minicamp. New coach Brian Daboll said Toney still hasn't received the team's new playbook.

"Like I said, this is a voluntary camp," Daboll said on Wednesday. "The guys that are here, we're going to work with. The guys that aren't, they're going to miss out on some things. It's voluntary for a reason. That's the nature of the rules.

"I've had good talks with K.T., good talks with some of the other guys. I'm encouraged with where we are with our participation, what we've been doing. We're going to keep working in the right direction."

Toney wasn't the only player that didn't attend the minicamp.

"It's voluntary," Schoen said. "Nobody asked about the other guys that aren't here. It's life. Life happens.

"I've had good conversations with Kadarius. We've been in contact. At the end of the day it's voluntary. That's what it is."
	
    
    <post>
		<date>April 21, 2022</date>
		<author>Adam Teicher</author>
		<title id = 2>Cheifs not rebuilding</title>
		<summary>Kansas City Chiefs not in 'rebuilding mode' despite losing key players, GM says</summary>
		<body>KANSAS CITY, Mo. -- The Kansas City Chiefs traded Tyreek Hill and opted not to re-sign Tyrann Mathieu. They have some seemingly obvious holes on their roster just a few days before the 2022 NFL draft.

General manager Brett Veach still resisted the idea the Chiefs are in any kind of rebuilding effort.

"When you have Pat Mahomes, we'll be wired to go after it every year,'' Veach said. "Even though you may make moves and you may trade really good players, it doesn't mean [there won't] be another counterpunch and that we [won't] try to be aggressive in another way. You just have to be smart and flexible in what you do. What's needed to do that is draft resources and cap space.

"Just because you trade away a great player doesn't mean we're in a rebuilding mode by any means. It just means we're going to find a new set of resources and we're going to try to be aggressive.''

The Chiefs after losing Hill, Mathieu and starting cornerback Charvarius Ward look to need help at wide receiver and in the secondary. They also need edge rushers to improve a pass rush that was 29th in the league last season in sacks.

The Chiefs did sign wide receivers JuJu Smith-Schuster and Marquez Valdes-Scantling and safety Justin Reid. But after losing Hill and two of last season's other top receivers, and being without Mathieu, Ward and one of last season's top defensive backs in terms of playing time in Daniel Sorensen, the Chiefs could still use help.

They have a league-high 12 draft picks, including two in each of the first four rounds.

As for replacing Hill, Veach said, "On one end, it's very hard to replicate a talent like Tyreek Hill. But I also think there's a mindset or idea forgetting how good a coach Andy Reid is. He's won with all types of quarterback and all different types of offensive schemes.

"Our staff is very dynamic and, look, we had Tyreek Hill and we were able to implement a lot of RPO stuff and a lot of vertical attack stuff, but it doesn't mean when you have a talent like Pat Mahomes and a Hall of Fame coach like Andy that you can't rewire and retweak your offense and how you do things. There are multiple ways we scored points over the years.

"Would you like to find someone like Tyreek? Yeah, but I think every team would. If you don't, there are many ways to win games. Our offense is I think extremely flexible, a lot more flexible than what people think. For us and what we do, we're going to go out there and collect good players. They might not be 4.2 guys but if they're good football players, we're going to put them into position to make plays and win a lot of games.''</body>
	</post>
	
    
    <post>
		<date>APril 22, 2022</date>
		<author>Jordan Raanan</author>
		<title id = 3>Logan Ryan files greivance</title>
		<summary>New Tampa Bay Buccaneers safety Logan Ryan files grievance against New York Giants, source says</summary>
		<body>Tampa Bay Buccaneers safety Logan Ryan filed a grievance against the New York Giants after being cut last month, a source confirmed to ESPN on Friday.

Ryan had $5.5 million of his 2022 salary with the Giants guaranteed. He had $8.5 million guaranteed for injury, and the veteran safety had offseason surgery. The dispute appears to be over the final $3 million.

The Athletic first reported the grievance.

The Giants signed Ryan to a three-year extension worth up to $30 million on Christmas Day 2020. However, coach Judge, who had history with Ryan from New England, was fired after this past season and Ryan was cut, despite New York saving just under $800,000 against the salary cap.

"Best decision for the New York Giants," general manager Joe Schoen said recently at the NFL's annual meetings. "We thought it was best; the new staff thought it was best. I wish Logan nothing but the best."

Ryan, 31, a New Jersey native, was a team captain with the Giants.

"It wasn't my call," Ryan said of his release during his introductory news conference with the Bucs.

Ryan was released after the start of free agency and eventually landed with Tampa Bay on a one-year deal worth the veteran minimum of $1.12 million.</body>
	</post>
</blog>